Checklist:
	>X-box outline
	>X-flip when clicked
		>X-when two are face up, check if match.
			>X-if both images have the same variable assignment, then they match.
			>X-find variable that contains the image, and then check if the second image returns the same variable
		>X-if match, leave face up and score.
                	>X-match = check if both cards have the same variable assignment.
		>X-if no match, flip back
	>X-randomizer(I did this first lol oops I just noticed it's an enhancement halfway through. Oh well ¯\_(ツ)_/¯)
		>X-in initialize
                >X-have variables that store images individually.
		>X-assign a variable to each img id randomly, correspond to img src
                	>X-the same image srcs will have the same variable
	>X-reset button
	>X-player click count
		>X-scoreboard & score mngmt
			>X-scoreboard
			>X-score management
	>X-instructions
	>X-page layout and style
		>X-dark and light mode
			>X-dark
			>X-light

Enhancements:
	>X-randomizer
	>X-hot computer flames
		>X-and comments
		>X-depending on how well the player is doing, give either statements of encouragement or discouragement.
			>X-encouragement when low, discouragement when high
			>X-the lower the score, the better. 
			-comments during gameplay?

			NO-give computer a personality; make it completely belittle the player for being human
				and claim that AIs will take over the world soon
				NO-it has a challenge for it
				NO-the words of encouragement are kind of sarcastic; mocking tone


	